<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>julianwest.me.blog</title>
    <link>https://julianwest.me/Blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content on julianwest.me.blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:04:18 -0600</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="https://julianwest.me/Blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Site Disclosure</title>
      <link>https://julianwest.me/Blog/site-disclosure/site-disclosure/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:04:18 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://julianwest.me/Blog/site-disclosure/site-disclosure/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;The opinions expressed on julianwest.me are solely my own and do not reflect the views of my employer, my friends and relatives, or any other carbon-based lifeform.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I may occasionally review products that I personally purchased or already own. I will not respond to solicitations to review products, nor do I accept loaner/demo products to review or blog about.&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I own, or have owned, some stock in a few of the tech companies I routinely blog, brag, or rant about including: Microsoft, Cisco, Apple, IBM, Solar City, and Tesla.&lt;br&gt;&#xA;As an information technology professional who often works under various NDAs, I adhere to employer policies governing blogging. Consequently I do not discuss my employers, projects, nor will I comment on past or present matters protected by attorney/client privelege.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Contact</title>
      <link>https://julianwest.me/Blog/contact/contacting/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 15:00:09 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://julianwest.me/Blog/contact/contacting/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;contacting-me-br-br-&#34;&gt;Contacting Me… &lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I welcome and look forward to questions or comments (good or bad) about julianwest.me, so feel free to write me, DM, etc.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;I do receive a fair amount of email every day. If I don’t respond to your email quickly, or if my response is indefinitely delayed, please don’t be offended. It’s possible I may missed your email, but try to read all email and chances are I will see it.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;Note to IT job recruiters: please do not write to me at my personal email address (unless you’re Apple, Google, or Cisco you’ll probably hit a filter), and instead please make any unsolicited correspondence via my LinkedIn profile. I answer all messages eventually. Thanks.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Colophon</title>
      <link>https://julianwest.me/Blog/colophon/colophon/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:57:42 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://julianwest.me/Blog/colophon/colophon/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This is the personal blog and web site of Julian West. More about Julian &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.com&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt; Site Disclosure &lt;a href=&#34;https://example.com&#34;&gt;here.&lt;/a&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;julian.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Alt text&#34;&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Hosting = Github Pages.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;Blog CMS is Hugo static site generator framework, running as a GitHub Pages workflow.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;Articles are typically drafted in Scrivener, archived in Day One journal.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;julianwest.me is best-viewed in a standards-compliant web browser (Safari or Chrome/Edge/etc).&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&#xA;If you’re using a recent browser and have problems navigating my site or blog, do let me know.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://julianwest.me/Blog/about/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 25 Nov 2024 14:57:32 -0600</pubDate>
      <guid>https://julianwest.me/Blog/about/about/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h3 id=&#34;_julian-west-is-a-north-texas-network-engineer-musician-and-writer_&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Julian West is a North Texas network engineer, musician, and writer.&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h3&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;&lt;img src=&#34;julian-about.jpeg&#34; alt=&#34;Alt text&#34;&gt;&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;h4 id=&#34;_trivial-stuff_&#34;&gt;&lt;em&gt;Trivial stuff&lt;/em&gt;&lt;/h4&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;I am a working-glass geek into technology, art, and good design.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I was raised in rural Texas by parents who were both born before 1931 (I am late for everything).&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I am a self-made man with all the past mistakes to prove it. I keep growing and learning every day.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I endured a term of poverty growing up, including a very brief period of homelessness. It was an education I wouldn’t trade for anything.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;  &lt;br&gt;&#xA;Writing code changed my life along with curiosity, Macs, and PCs.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;Myers-Briggs says I am INTP, but I like people. At least the cool ones.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;My close friends call me “Jules”, maybe seven people. The cool ones.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;For a living I’m an ops nerd and I manage IT network projects &amp;amp; deployments.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I am, despite the Cisco/Microsoft/Linux IT gig, a huge Apple geek. This is not an uncommon thing nowadays.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;I drive an electric car built in California which unfortunately transformed an autistic immigant billionaire into a problematic Oligarch. Still pondering that one.&lt;!-- raw HTML omitted --&gt;&lt;br&gt;&#xA;For hobbies I write and strum a guitar and develop messy PowerShell and Python code.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
